Obey the rules.
Sleuth is a drama, mystery, thriller film directed by Kenneth Branagh.
Locked in a high-tech English manor, bound in a deadly duel of wits, Andrew Wyke and Milo Tindle come together
as English gentlemen to discuss the matter of Wyke's wife: the woman both are sleeping with.
Andrew Wyke, played by Michael Caine.
Milo Tindle, played by Jude Law.
Man on T.V., played by Harold Pinter.
Maggie, played by Carmel O'Sullivan.
Other Man on T.V., played by Kenneth Branagh.
Sleuth is a 2007 thriller film directed by Kenneth Branagh
and starring Jude Law and Michael Caine.
The screenplay by Harold Pinter is an adaptation
of Anthony Shaffer's play, Sleuth.
Caine had previously starred in a 1972 version, where he
played Law's role against Laurence Olivier.
The film explores themes of age difference, female lover,
insurance fraud, based on play or musical, remake.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.